RABBITLAND
Rabbitland.
兔子大地。
Nothing can change the wonderful impression.
沒有什麼可以改變兔子大地完美的外觀。
Rabbits live in comfy pink homes.
兔子們住在舒適的粉紅色家裡面。
Rabbits are happy.
兔子們很開心。
And since they have no brains,
而且因為他們沒有腦，
just holes in their heads
只有一個大洞在頭上，
Nothing bad can happen to them.
不管什麼事情發生對他們來說都不算是壞事。
They are the most perfect and highest stage in evolution.
他們進化到了最完美而最高的境界。
Rabbits rise very early each morning,
兔子們每天都起的非常早。
put heavy blank sheets of paper
把一疊厚厚的空白紙
in the holes in their heads,
塞在他們頭上的洞裡。
gather around the huge golden monument
聚在巨大的金色紀念碑旁邊
and patiently wait for
然後耐心的等候....
the play button to be pressed.
[開始]鍵被按下。
And then, slowly and orderly, they start.
然後，緩慢而有順序的，他們開始了。
The journey is long
旅程是漫長的
suprising
充滿驚喜的
with many obstacles
還有各種障礙
IQ measuring points, but
還有智力測驗，但是
despite that, the Rabbits travel slowly and dutifully,
除了這些，兔子們的旅程是緩慢的義務之旅
with a clear goal.
有著一個明確的目的
They go far, far away,
他們旅行到好遠好遠的地方，
up to the borders of Rabbitland,
直到兔子大地的邊境
even though beyond them there is nothing
即使等著他們的什麼都沒有
but only empty areas, inhabited by
只有一大片空地，屬於....
Evil Girls.
邪惡女孩幫
They go so far to vote at the elections,
他們來到這麼遠的地方只為了在選舉中投票，
which in Rabbitland take place once a day,
這樣的選舉在兔子大地天都會舉行
because it is a well-ordered democracy.
因為這是一個井然有序的民主社會
Remarkably easily,
這一切誇張的輕鬆。
one by one,
一個接著一個
they insert the ballots
他們把選票
into a tall, tall ballot box.
投進一個很高很高的選票箱。
The Evil Girls know that every vote is a vote for them.
邪惡女孩幫知道每一張選票都是投給她們的。
The Rabbits return home full of joy.
兔子們開心的回家了。
And then, the Evil Girls press stop,
然後，邪惡女孩幫按下[停止]鍵，
and the evening comes to Rabbitland.
此時兔子大地的傍晚也會來到。
The Rabbits go to sleep.
兔子們接著就去睡覺了。
But, having no brain, they can't sleep.
但，因為沒有大腦，他們無法入睡。
so they watch the election results
所以他們只好看電視上的
on TV the whole night.
選舉結果看個整晚。
At the borders of Rabbitland, the Evil Girls play
在兔子大地的邊境，邪惡女孩幫嬉鬧著
and they laugh at another senseless day.
然後他們嘲笑著另一個毫無意義的一天。
The Rabbits are happy.
兔子們很快樂。
Happy day in Rabbitland.
又是兔子大地快樂的一天。
happy
快樂